JORGE **MARTINEZ**

WEB DEVELOPER / 29 YEARS OLD



HELLO.. MY Name is Jorge Luis Martinez Mendoza. I consider myself a pro-active person, I am a responsible and self-taught person, I like to learn new things to improve both professionally and personally, with over 5 years of experience working in web development mainly Full Stack, now focusing on Front End

Mail: jorgelmtz93@gmail.com Phone: +523323773263 Addreess: Los Olivos, Tlaquepaque, Jal.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Apr 2022 - Present

Netcommerce/ Av. 16 de Septiembre 730, 44180 Guadalajara, Jal. Developed and maintained websites for different customers.

Full Stack Developer (Freelance)

Oct 2021 - Jan 2022

We-know / Calle de la Nebulosa 2870, 44520 Guadalajara, Jal.

Developed and designed their ERP to manage customers data, hosting and resources.

Front-End Developer

Oct 2020 - Oct 2021

*Industrias Lior / Av. 5 de Febrero 554, 44460 Guadalajara, Jal.*Developed and designed UI for their store, backoffice and other websites.

Full Stack Developer

Dec 2017 - Aug 2020

We-know / Calle de la Nebulosa 2870, 44520 Guadalajara, Jal.

Developed and maintained custom products for different clients using LMS Moodle.

E-commerce Developer

Jun 2017 - Dec 2017

Enature / Av. Tepeyac 1645, 45230 Zapopan, Jal. Developed custom modules for their e-commerce store using magento.

Full Stack Developer

May 2015 - Aug 2016

Indat / Calle Lope de Vega 217, 44130 Guadalajara, Jal.

Developed and maintained websites for different government institutions of the state of Jalisco.

EDUCATION

Information and Communication Technology (Engineering)

Universidad Tecnologica de Jalisco Sep 2015 - Mar 2017

Information and Communication Technology (TSU)

Universidad Tecnologica de Jalisco Sep 2013 - Aug 2015

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- SASS/LESS
- Javascript (ES6)
- PHP
- ¡Query
- GIT
- Bootstrap / Tailwind
- MYSQL/SQL
- Moodle
- REST
- English (Int. / Adv.)
- Laravel

EXTRAS

- Codeigniter
- ReactJS
- AngularJS
- NodeJS
- Android
- Java
- IT
- SCRUM